B1 David, Nora and Millie are talking about some of the world's greatest ecosystems.
Listen to their conversation.
Write a T if a sentence is true, or an F if it is false.
Then correct the false ones.
Hey David and Millie, do you know any of the biggest ecosystems on Earth?
Yes, I know about the Amazon rainforest.
It's the largest rainforest in the world.
It covers around 6 million square kilometers.
Yes, it's huge!
It's a very important ecosystem of our planet with so many different types of wildlife.
There's also the Sahara Desert.
It's the largest hot desert in the world.
It covers most of Northern Africa.
That's such a big area!
Now, what about the ocean ecosystem?
I know the Great Barrier Reef in Australia.
It's the biggest coral reef system anywhere.
By the way, did you know that Lake Baikal is the deepest lake in the world?
No, where is it?
It's in Russia.
I'd love to see it someday.